本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版
-嗨  艾薇  -嘿
-Hi, Ivy. -Hey.
-嗨  GG  -莱娜  我知道你是新生
-Hi, G.G. -Lana, I know you're new here,
但是我的名字是泰迪
But my name is Teddy.
抱歉  我听到很多人都叫你GG
I'm sorry. I've just heard so many people call you "G. G.,"
-所以我以为  -不是的  我叫泰迪
-I thought... -No, it's Teddy.
知道了  泰迪  “泰”字开头
Got it. Teddy. Starts with a "t."
就像太敏感
Just like touchy.
艾薇  为什么大家叫我GG
Ivy, why are people calling me gigi?
俺哪知道  可能是外号什么的吧
I don't know. Maybe it's a nickname.
这个“GG”是个名字
Are they saying gigi like the name "gigi"
还是个缩写
Or the letters "G. G."?
俺哪知道  也许是缩写吧
I don't know. Probably the second one.
那这个缩写代表的是什么呢
What would G.G. stand for?
魅力女郎
Glamorous gal.
金色女神
Golden goddess.
伟大基因
Genetic greatness.
乖乖女
Goody-goody.
意思是乖乖女
It means goody-goody.
乖乖女  为什么这么叫我
Goody-goody... why would they call me that?
因为你总是循规蹈矩
Maybe it's because you always play by the rules.
从不做坏事
And never do anything bad.
类似于坏事的事情
Or something like that.
是吗  但我并不是那么的乖乖女啊
Okay, but I am so not a goody-goody.
从某种程度上说  我算是个坏坏女
If anything, I am a baddy-baddy.
小泰  只有乖乖女
T, only a goody-goody.
才用坏坏女这个词
Would say baddy-baddy.
我做过坏事  我违反过规定
I've been bad. I've broken rules.
-哪次  -就是那次
-Like when? -Like the time...
-我曾挑战过规定的灰色地带  -哪次
-Okay, I've bent rules. -Like when?
就是那次
Like the time...
我滴个乖乖
Oh, man.
我就是个GG
I am a G.G.
真高兴你欣然接受了
I'm glad you came around, girl.
因为这事是我起的头
'Cause I'm the one who started it.
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
校订： line
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z  liloelva
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第二季第二十三集
Good Luck Charlie  S02E23  Ditch Day
老弟  我需要你的帮助
Gabe, I need your help.
我刚知道我有了一个惨不忍闻的外号
So I just found out I have this horrible nickname.
你是指GG
You mean G.G.?
你怎么知道的
How do you know about that?
我帮艾薇想出来的
I helped Ivy come up with it.
好了  总之  我并不是乖乖女
Okay, well, I'm not a goody-goody.
我要做一些出格的事情来证明
And I wanna do something naughty to prove it.
首先  不要用出格这类词汇
First, stop using words like naughty.
明白了
Got it.
我会帮你变邪恶的  但你也要帮我点事情
Now I'll help you be bad, But you gotta help me with something.
-什么事  -那个  我被禁足了
-What? -Well, I'm grounded,
但是我周六有活动
But I need to get ungrounded by Saturday.
杰克请我去冒险天地
Jake invited me to super adventure land.
冒险天地又开张了吗
Super adventure land reopened?
是啊  所以我要在再关张之前再去一次
Yeah, that's why I got there before they close down again.
我如何才能让爸妈给我亮绿灯
Now how do I get mom and dad to let me go?
容易  你可以表现得乖点儿
Well, you could try behaving better.
别闹了  没时间开玩笑了  我需要答案
All right, I don't have time for joke. I need answers.
你可以讨好他们啊
Why don't you just do something nice for them?
-比如  -比如上星期在车库
-Like? -I was in the garage last week.
然后我找到了老爸写给老妈的一首老诗《重返高中》
And I found this old poem the dad wrote to mom Back In High School.
我准备在生日的时候送给她
I was gonna give it to her for her birthday,
但是你可以借花献佛
But you could do it now.
然后他们就乖乖的听我话了
Then they'll be putty in my hands.
-谢了  GG  -别这么叫我
-Thanks, G.G. -Stop calling me that.
-嗨  查莉  -嗨  GG
-Hi, Charlie. -Hi, G.G.
可恶
Argh!
老妈  能给我做条裙子吗
Mom, will you make me a dress?
PJ  需要谈谈吗
P.J., do we need to talk?
谈什么
About what?
谈谈要让我给你弄条裙子这件事
About why you want me to make you a dress.
不是让你  是需要你
I don't want you to. I need you to.
孩子  就不能借一条我的吗
Honey, can't you just borrow one of mine?
这只是一个阶段而已
This could just be a phase.
裙子不是给我的
The dress isn't for me.
是给查莉的
It's for Charlie.
我的家政课作业是为家里的某个人
I got an assignment in my home ec class to make an outfit.
做一件服饰
For someone in my family.
明白了  但是下次请提前说这句话
Okay, next time lead with that.
那你帮我吗
So will you do it?
不  如果我帮你做  你还怎么从中学习
Nope, if I do it, how will you learn?
老妈  我上这课就是为了接近女生
Mom, I took this class to meet girls,
不是为了学习
Not to learn stuff.
我都上了三年的家政课了
It's my third year taking home ec,
我都不知道这门课是干什么的
And I still don't know what "ec" means.
抱歉了  孩子  你要靠自己了
Sorry, kiddo. You're on your own.
好吧  好吧  那你能帮我完成内战报告吗
Fine. Well, then will you help me with my civil war report?
没戏
Nope.
至少告诉我谁赢了总可以吧
Will you at least tell me who won?
我想到了个大胆的计划
I've got a daring new plan.
绝对会完全摆脱乖乖女这个外号
That's gonna blow away my goody-goody image forever.
准备好洗耳恭听
Are you ready for this?
明天
Tomorrow,
-我们翘课  -好啊
-I say we ditch school. -Okay.
艾薇  你是不是没明白我在说什么啊
Ivy, I don't think you understand what I'm proposing here.
我说明天
I'm saying tomorrow.
我们不会在学校里
We're not going to be in school.
即使在上课
When school is going on.
小泰  我了解翘课是什么意思
T, I'm familiar with the concept of ditching.
那我们去哪疯
So where are we going?
-冒险天地  -没问题
-Super adventure land. -I'm in.
好了  艾薇  一言为定
Okay, Ivy, it's settled.
我们明天就翘课
We are going to ditch school tomorrow.
没听错
That's right.
就是明天  泰迪和艾薇  翘课
Tomorrow, Teddy, Ivy ditching.
翘课
And by ditching,
意味着逃学  逃课
I mean gone. Not here.
缺勤
Abse<i>sans</i> excuse.
我们知道了  泰迪  你要翘课
We got it, Teddy. You're ditching.
是啊  明天我就要有个新外号了
Yeah, by tomorrow I'm gonna have a new nickname.
逃课小姐
Gone girl.
依旧是GG
That's still G.G.
可恶
Agggghh!
好了  查莉  我要给你设计条裙子
Okay, Charlie, I'm gonna design a dress for you.
不用担心  我已经看了十个小时的时尚真人秀节目
Now don't worry. I just watched 10 hours of fashion reality shows.
所以我已经有很高的品味了
So I'm highly qualified.
现在让我们来看看你平常都穿些什么
Now let's start by taking a look at what you usually wear.
好的  算了
Okay, no.
糟糕
Wrong.
扔掉  小朋友  你在想些什么
Hate it. Girlfriend, what are you thinking?
猫头鹰早过时了
Owls are so last year.
乖乖  我要把你打扮得脱胎换骨
Honey, we need to create a whole new look for you,
打扮成惊世查莉
Something that screaming<i>charlie!</i>
噢  抱歉  我惊到“查莉”了
Oh, sorry I screamed "charlie."
如果我要给你打造一条完美的裙子
If I'm gonna make you the perfect dress,
我就需要深入的了解你
I need to know more about you.
告诉我你喜欢什么
So tell me what you like.
我喜欢玩具
I like toys.
玩具  乐趣
Toys. Fun.
青春  我想到了
Youth. I'm getting something.
等等  好的  好的
Wait a second. Yes. Yes!
这就是你的新形象
That's your new look.
不要
No.
你给我耍天后作风
You are such a diva.
我喜欢
I love it.
老妈  老爸  我感到很抱歉
Mom, dad, I was feeling so bad.
不管我做了什么而导致了关禁闭
About whatever I did to get grounded.
你用花园水管喷达布尼夫人
You sprayed Mrs. Dabney with a garden hose.
纯属意外
It was an accident.
当时她在厨房里
She was in her kitchen.
总之  我对此事很抱歉
Anyway, I felt so bad about that,
所以我决定主动去清扫车库
That I decided to clean the garage.
然后我在老妈的小盒子里发现了这个
And I found this in one of mom's little boxes.
-还特意裱好了给你  -什么东西
-And framed it for you. -What is it?
是高中的时候  老爸写给老妈的一首情诗
It's a love poem dad wrote to mom in High School.
别  别  别  你不用读出来  盖比
No no no. You don't have to read it, Gabe.
“我那亲爱的艾米  梦想怎能在沙滩上留下足印”
"my dearest Amy, how does a dream leave footprints in the sand?"
花朵怎能唤起一段回忆
How does a flower kindle a memory.
“或者烛光细语着你的名字”
"Or candlelight whisper your name?"
写得不赖  是吧
Pretty good so far, huh?
不赖  我都听迷糊了
Pretty good? I'm a plate of soup.
我怎么不记着写过这些
I don't remember writing that.
这诗根本都不押韵
It doesn't even rhyme like a good poem should.
看看啊  这都不是我的笔迹
Look at that. That's not even my handwriting.
老爸  这是你写的  还署名“鲍伯”
Dad, you wrote it. It's signed "Bob D."
除了你还有谁是“鲍伯”
Who else would "Bob D." be?
大混球
Diddlebock.
嘿  老爸  说话注意点
Hey, dad, watch the language.
为什么大混球鲍伯
Why would Bob diddlebock.
给你写了首情诗
Write you a love poem?
听着  在那段时间里
Okay, during that brief time.
就是高中咱俩分手的那段时间里
In High School when we were broken up,
我和大混球鲍伯约了约会  没什么大不了的
I dated Bob diddlebock. It was no big deal.
大不过大混球鲍伯
Not to Bob diddlebock.
你就是那个在他的沙滩里留下足印的
You were a dream that left footprints.
梦想
In his sand.
老娘我的确具备那种魅力
I do have that effect on men.
哇  哇  在我们分手后
Whoa whoa! So the minute we break up,
你马上就去外面找新男友了
You go out and find another guy?
那我该怎么办  回家后以泪洗面吗
What was I supposed to do? Go home and cry all day?
我就是啊
I did.
鲍伯  都过了二十年了  就忘了这件事吧
Bob, it's been 20 years. Let it go.
就像你忘了这首诗一样
Like you let the poem go?
当时我们分手了
We were on a break.
-不如我们都另结新欢  -没问题啊
-How about we take another one? -Works for me.
同志们啊  这本应该
Guys, this was supposed.
是个欢乐的时刻
To be a happy moment.
对于我来说
For me!
噢  学校开课了
Oh! School's just starting.
第一节课  开始了
First period is happening right now.
恭喜了  小泰  你终于翘课了
Congratulations, t. You're officially ditching.
当回坏坏女感觉如何啊
How does it feel to be bad?
好极了
Great.
你的胃和我一样疼吗
Does your stomach hurt as much as mine?
好啊  小姐们
Howdy, young ladies!
我是冒险天地的园长
I'm the mayor of super adventure land.
-你是哪位啊  -俺叫艾薇
-Who are you? -I'm Ivy.
呃  我是克劳德特
Uh... I'm Claudette.
来自俄克拉荷马州
I'm from Oklahoma.
我父母没在
My parents aren't here right now.
他们带我的弟弟  铁锈和灰尘去洗手间了
They're taking my brothers Rusty and Dusty to the bathroom.
好了  你的自我介绍好详细啊
Well, that's a little more information.
可我不需要  亲爱的
Than I needed, darling.
你脑袋有问题吗  克劳德特
What is wrong with you, Claudette?
应付这种事情我还是新手
I'm new at this, okay?
条子盯上我们了
A cop is staring at us.
他绝对知道我们翘课了
He totally knows we're ditching.
小泰  淡定  他才不关心咱俩呢
T, will you stop? He doesn't care about us.
那他为什么走过来了
Then why is he coming over here?
放松  没事的
Just be cool. Nobody's in trouble.
小姐们  你们被捕了
Young ladies, you're under arrest.
我们被捕了
We're under arrest?
-恐怕是的  -为什么
-Afraid so. -For what?
因为玩得不够开心
For not having enough fun.
作为冒险天地的警长
And as sheriff of super adventure land,
我要给你们一张
I'm gonna have to give you a ticket.
注：ticket还有罚单的意思
免费的冰沙兑换券
For a free smoothie.
现在咱们能好好去娱乐下了吗
Now can we please go have some fun?
我想玩恐怖云霄飞车
I wanna ride terror in the sky.
是吗
Really?
但是我想玩花栗鼠先生怪怪小丑车
'cause I was thinking Mr. Chipmunk's kooky clown cars.
好吧  那我去找铁锈和灰尘了
Yeah, I'm gonna go find Rusty and Dusty.
老爸  快看看我在车库里找到的老相册
Dad, check out this old photo album I found in the garage.
你给我离车库远点
You stay out of the garage.
里面充满了悲剧
It's full of misery.
看看你和老妈在一起时的美好时光
Let's look at all the great times you and mom have had.
嘿  这张是你和老妈和一群帅小伙在毕业舞会上
Hey, there's you and mom and some handsome guy at the prom.
那就是大混球鲍伯
That's Bob diddlebock.
下一张
Moving on.
嘿  老妈哪里弄的这辆跑车
Hey, where'd mom get that really cool sports car?
是大混球鲍伯的
That's Bob diddlebock's.
他有两辆
He had two.
好了  再看下一张
All right, let's try one more.
你曾经有没有过一艘
Any chance you had a boat.
叫大混球鲍伯的船
Called the s.S. Diddlebock?
说真的
You know,
真不敢相信她一直保留着这首诗
I just can't believe she kept his poem all these years.
总之  还是要谢谢你哄我开心  盖比
Anyway, thanks for cheering me up, Gabe.
英俊  潇洒  有钱
Handsome, smart and rich.
噢  艾米  你怎么就这么放弃他了
Oh, Amy, how did you let him get away?
嘿  老妈
Hey, mom.
你知道周六前应该做什么事情吗
You know what would be a really cool thing to do before Saturday?
-什么事情  -在老爸面前撕掉大混球鲍伯的情诗
-What's that? -Rip up Bob diddlebock's poem in front of dad.
告诉他这都成为过往云烟了
Show him it means nothing to you.
盖比  我不会这么做的
Gabe, I'm not gonna do that.
为什么
Why?
难道因为你还对他有感觉吗
Because you still have feelings for him?
难道你都潜伏在厨房里吗
So now you're lurking in the kitchen?
嘿  我一直喜欢呆在厨房里
Hey, I am always in the kitchen.
只不过这次碰巧潜伏了一次
I just happened to be lurking this one time.
快回答我的问题
You just answer the question.
没有  我对大混球鲍伯没有感觉了
No, I do not have feelings for Bob diddlebock.
那你为什么一直留着这首诗
Then why did you keep his stupid poem all these years?
因为这是我收到过的唯一一首情诗  这就是原因
Because it's the only love poem anyone ever wrote me. That's why.
噢  是吗  那个  那个
Oh, yeah? Well, that's... that's...
的确说得在理
That's a pretty good reason.
天啊  心里不好受啊
Man, now I just feel bad.
知道吗  解决心情郁闷的最好方法就是
You know, the best way to get over feeling bad is.
让别人心情愉快
To make someone else feel good.
我就是别人
I can be that someone.
不行吗  好吧
No? Okay.
我们下一个玩什么
So where should we go next?
说茄子
Say cheese!
祝你玩得开心
Have a super day!
艾薇
Ivy!
-你刚才看见了吗  -看见什么
-Did you see that? -See what?
谁想和我照相啊  请上前来
Who wants to take a picture with me? Step right up.
嘿  我识破你的阴谋了
Hey, I saw what you did!
你偷了那个女人的钱包
You stole that woman's wallet.
我不知道你在说什么  再见了
I don't know what you're talking about. Toodle-oo!
嘿  你给我回来
Hey, come back here.
这到底怎么回事
What in tarnation is going on here?
这个园长  是个贼  他偷了一个女人的钱包
The mayor, he's a thief. He stole a woman's wallet.
-什么  -小心  比尔
-What? -Careful, Bill.
我看她今天一直不正常  可能是六号
She's been acting up all day. Might be a code 6.
-跟我走  -等一下
-Let's go. -Wait a minute.
六号是什么
What's a code 6?
神经病
Possible wacko!
查莉怎么没去幼儿园
Why isn't Charlie in preschool?
我把她接出来了  我们要忙些事情
I had to pull her out. We have work to do.
你怎么也没去上学
Why aren't you in school?
查莉的裙子没做好  我要抓紧时间赶工了
Charlie's dress isn't done, and I'm on a deadline.
好吧  难道我的孩子都没上学吗
Okay, are any of my kids in school?
至少我清楚泰迪在学校
At least I know Teddy is.
老妈  我快抓狂了  你能帮我看下裙子吗
Mom, I'm freaking out. Would you mind taking a look at my dress?
好啊  让我看看你的杰作
Sure, let's see what you got.
这全怪查莉
It's all Charlie's fault.
穿在她身上就展现不出来
She's not selling it.
别指责你的模特
Don't blame the model.
我说要表现出凶悍  你这是凶悍吗
I said be fierce. Is that fierce?
我不知道
I don't know.
不是  你这不是凶悍
No, you don't, do you?
这  这简直就是场灾难
This... this is a disaster.
艾薇  你一定要把我弄出去
Ivy, you gotta get me out of here.
我还没做好蹲监狱的准备
I am not cut out for the slammer.
别慌  俺来搞定
Don't worry. I've got this.
好的
Okay.
好啊  警长
Howdy, sheriff.
哎呦
Whoops.
警长  你是不是掉了两百游戏币啊
Sheriff, I think you dropped 200 fun bucks there.
你想贿赂我吗
Are you trying to bribe me?
也许是啊
Maybe I am.
游戏币又不能当钱花
With pink money that has absolutely no monetary value?
我是警长  我马上到
Sheriff. I'm on my way.
好了  算你们走运
Well, it's your lucky day.
我们这里人手不足  还抓到了个十二号
We're understaffed. We just got a code 12.
什么是十二号
What's that?
有孩子在旋转座椅上吐了
Some kid just barfed on the tilt-a-whirl.
现在你们可以走了
Now you're free to go.
谢天谢地
Thank goodness.
PJ  我们在等着呢
P.J., we're waiting.
好了
All right.
欢迎我们的
Say hello.
查莉
To Charlie.
这条靓丽的夏日裙子非常适合两岁的儿童
Her kicky summer dress is perfect for the 2 year old.
可以满足精力旺盛的孩子
Who plays all day and parties all night.
从小憩时间到零食时间
From nap time to snack time,
这条裙子全部搞定
This dress says it all.
如果不慎将果汁洒到裙子上面了
And if there's an oopsie with a juice box,
不用担心  一洗就干净
No problem. It's washable.
不得不承认  这让我大吃一惊
I have to say I am impressed.
整洁的线条  精妙的剪裁
Clean lines, nice stitching.
杰作
Excellent job.
谢谢  也要谢谢你  查莉
Thank you and thank you, Charlie.
耶
Yeah.
那是标价签吗
Is that a price tag?
成了  B减
All right, "b" minus.
没搞错吧  噢  难道因为买成品
Really? Oh, because buying the dress.
是一种具有创造性的解决问题的方法
Is a creative way to solve the problem?
不是  因为这是你第三次选这门课了
No, because this is your third time in my class.
以后我们别见面了
We're done.
大家好
Hello!
有人能借我下笔记吗
Can I borrow someone's notes?
抱歉  不知道你们有没有发觉
Sorry, I don't know if you guys noticed.
昨天我没来上学
I wasn't here yesterday.
没错  翘课了
That's right. Ditching.
是啊  你说过了
Yeah, you told us that.
我们去了冒险天地
We went to super adventure land,
和条子发生了点争执
Had a bit of a run-in with the cops,
最后还蹲了监狱
Ended up in jail.
小泰  看
T, look.
-他怎么来了  -泰迪·邓肯  能过来一下吗
-What is he doing here? -Teddy Duncan, would you come up here, please?
大家好  我是冒险天地的警长
Hello, I am the sheriff of super adventure land.
因为这位小姐
And because of this young lady,
我们破获了一起连环盗窃案
We uncovered a ring of pickpockets.
不幸的是  疑犯就包括我们的园长
That sadly included our own mayor,
街头公告员
The town crier.
对了  还有一只松鼠
And yes, sal the squirrel.
现在作为冒险天地
And now on behalf of super adventure land,
总公司  本行业  北美地区的代表
And our parent company, famfunco industries, north America,
颁发优秀市民奖牌
I'm proud to present this super citizen medal.
给泰迪·邓肯
To Teddy Duncan.
我不是优秀市民  我翘课了  我很坏的
I'm not a super citizen. I'm a ditcher. I'm bad.
成了  随便你了
Well, whatever you are,
感谢你给我们提供了一个健康安全的娱乐场所
Thank you for saving good wholesome clean family fun.
乖乖女  乖乖女
G.G.! G.G.!
大家  我很坏的
Guys, I'm bad!
我跟你们说  我坏到骨子里
I'm bad I tell you!
乖乖女  乖乖女
G.G.! G.G.!
爱咋咋地
What the heck?
乖乖女  乖乖女
G.G.! G.G.!
嘿  艾米  你有时间吗
Hey, Amy, you got a minute?
-什么事啊  鲍伯  -让你听点东西
-What is it, Bob? -Something I want you to hear.
好了  我给你写了这东西
Okay, I wrote this for you.
“致我的贤妻”
"To my wonderful wife,"
我的挚爱
The love of my life,
这是你鲍比哥给你写的诗
Here is a poem from your bobby-boo.
我喜欢你的拥抱
I love your sweet hugs.
甚于我的虫子
Even more than my bugs.
“你的吻  胜过辣椒与炖肉”
"And your kisses more than chili or stew."
你最喜欢炖肉了
You do love your stew.
听着  还有呢  还有呢  听好了
Okay, here, there's more. There's more. Okay.
“尽管未来天注定”
"and though our future's unwritten,"
但是我的爱不会变
I still remain smitten.
直到永远
And will till the end of all time.
也许这首诗姗姗来迟
This poem may be late.
也许平淡无奇
I know it's not great,
“但至少我懂得如何押韵”
"But at least I know how to rhyme."
太贴心了
That's very sweet.
谢谢了  鲍比哥
Thank you, bobby-boo.
呃  我是说  发生了什么
Eww. I mean, what's going on?
我又收到了一首情诗
I have a new poem for my frame.
没错  而且很押韵
Yes, and it rhymes.
你俩和好了  太好了
You guys made up. That's just fantastic.
我提议  大家庆祝下
You know, we should celebrate.
冒险天地一日游如何啊
How about a trip to super adventure land?
好啊  没问题  我们好久都没去过了
Yeah, why not? We haven't been there in a while.
-是啊  我也同意  -万岁
-Yeah, sounds good to me. -Yes!
嘿  PJ  你猜怎么着
Hey, P.J., guess what.
咱们全家都要去冒险天地了
The whole family's going to super adventure land.
噢  你没听说吗
Oh, didn't you hear?
冒险天地的园长卷入了一场丑闻
There's a big scandal involving the mayor.
现在又关张了
Super adventure land's closed.
不要啊
No!
好了  查莉  老爸老妈发现我翘课了
Well, Charlie, mom and dad found out I ditched.
现在我被禁足了
And now I'm grounded.
报应来了
It's called consequences.
你要适应一下坏坏女的生活
Something you get used to when you're a baddy-baddy.
可恶  我还戴着奖牌呢
Darn, I'm still wearing the medal.
泰迪  你在干什么
Teddy, what are you doing?
被禁足期间不允许拍视频日记
No video diary while you're grounded.
No video diary while I'm grounded?
听起来好可笑啊
That seems kind of lame.
我不知道怎么惩罚你了
I don't know how else to punish you.
你总是很听话
You don't really do anything.
你认为我很乖吗
So you don't think I'm bad?
老妈  我坏到骨子里
Mom, I'm bad.
我坏到不和你说祝你好运  查莉
I'm so bad I'm not even gonna say good luck, Charlie.
-你刚说过了  -噢
-You just did. -Oh!
这个故事  真有其事
<i>The story you have just seen... it's true.</i>
结局完全是瞎编的
<i>The outcomes</i> <i>are completely made up.</i>
园长因说谎  盗窃
<i>The mayor was found</i> <i>guilty of lying, stealing</i>
用滑稽的卡通腔调说话而定罪
<i>And talking in a ridiculous</i> <i>cartoony voice.</i>
滑稽  我可不这么认为
Ridiculous?! I think not.
盖比·邓肯最终还是去了冒险天地
<i>Gabe Duncan eventually made it</i> <i>to super adventure land.</i>
但是在他游玩不久  就被关进了监狱
<i>He was thrown in jail</i> <i>three minutes later</i>
原因是在过山车上呕吐
<i>For spitting</i> <i>off the monorail.</i>
PJ·邓肯没能从事时装设计行业
<i>PJ Duncan did not go on a career in fashion design.</i>
艾米·邓肯
<i>Amy Duncan...</i>
只想照张相
<i>Just likes having a picture-taken.</i>